Contact

3 Hamlin Road East Brunswick NJ 7324348901 (Mobile) lab453@scarletmail.rutgers. edu

www.linkedin.com/in/ laurencebartram (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
React.js
REST APIs
Customer Service

LAURENCE BARTRAM

Computer Science Student at Rutgers University | Rutgers IT Help Desk Consultant

East Brunswick, New Jersey, United States

Summary

I'm a passionate Senior working on finishing my Computer Science degree at the Rutgers School of Arts and Sciences. I aspire to be hired as a Software Engineer and have experience developing applications in several programming languages, such as Java, JavaScript, C, and Python.

Throughout my coursework, I've gained experience working with UI/UX website and App development using React.js and REST API techniques. I've also had the opportunity to clean and manage large public data sets using the NumPy and Pandas Python libraries.

For the past 2 years, I have worked as an IT Consultant at Rutgers Office of Information Technology. My day to day responsibilities involve troubleshooting Rutgers account and device issues. As a long time employee, I help new consultants learn the ropes by answering any questions they may have, and providing them the necessary resources to solve customer issues. I intend to translate my troubleshooting and communication skills into my future career as a software developer.

Experience

Rutgers University–New Brunswick Information Technology Help Desk November 2021 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Piscataway, New Jersey, United States

- Troubleshoot device, software, and account issues of Rutgers students, staff, and guests.
- Assist individuals in person, over the phone, and through email.
- Utilize Slack to communicate with fellow consultants and supervisors.
- Utilize ServiceNow to create tickets and document progress in resolving client issues.
- Utilize Rutgers databases to determine the cause of client issues.

 Assist new consultants in troubleshooting difficult issues, and provide necessary documentation and support articles.

ShopRite

Store Cashier

August 2019 - February 2020 (7 months)

East Brunswick, New Jersey, United States

- Scanned and bagged customer's groceries.
- · Handled customer transactions.
- Returned unneeded items to store shelves.
- Assisted other cashiers in the "ShopRite From Home" department, where I completed online orders.

Education

Rutgers University-New Brunswick

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (September 2020 - May 2024)

East Brunswick High School

· (September 2017 - June 2020)